Hi, this is Liz Muller from Liz's Hair Design in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip we're going to show you how to care for African American hair and bi-racial hair.
This is an example of relaxed hair, African American hair.
And this young lady here, she actually treats her hair once a week.
She keeps it real moisturized, gets her hair washed and set once a week, and it's really important to do these things because you want to keep the hair in good condition.
It's very fragile when you get your hair relaxed, and you want to just treat it all the time, and if it's not relaxed too, you know, because maybe it doesn't it doesn't have a relaxer, it's courser, so you want to really add a lot of moisture to that hair because ethnic hair tends to get dry and you want to keep it conditioned to work better with it.
Actually, I use this beautiful Moroccan oil, and it's really wonderful on the hair.
It adds conditioning to the hair, and it leaves the hair in wonderful condition to work with.
I do it and I use it when I roll and set the hair, put a little bit in there, just about a dimes worth, and I rub it all over.
On mine I do the same thing, and that's bi-racial hair.
This is Liz Muller, and this is how to care for African American and bi-racial hair.